Activities and Organizations Records UA024
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Activities and organizations, 1857 -- 2019; UA024.001; 9.45 Linear Feet; 192 Digital Object(s)
  - Band, 1926 -- 1961; UA024.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
    - Marching Band, UA024.001.003.00001.00035; Unknown (Box 3)
      People; Music; Instruments
    - Band, UA024.001.003.00001.00036; Burdette & Co (Box 3)
    - Man conducting band, UA024.001.003.00001.00037; Unknown (Box 3)
      People; Music; Instruments; Building sites
  - Beelzebubs (1), 1965 -- 1984; UA024.001.003.00002 (Box 3)
    - Beelzebubs, 1967 -- 1968; UA024.001.003.00002.00001; Unknown (Box 3)
      Front seated on grass, left to right, Steve Beattie,John Zineto. Seated or standing in car, left to right Tom Finck, Mike Marino, Phil Luber, Fred Moore, John McCarthy, Harvey Lowd, Jim McCusker, Bill Hamilton, Art Evans, Fred Voos, Ted Piekos.
      Singers; Automobiles; Trees; People; Beezlebubs
    - Beelzebubs, 1969; UA024.001.003.00002.00002; Young, Donald T. (Box 3)
      Singers; People; Building sites; Beezlebubs
    - Beelzebubs, 1965; UA024.001.003.00002.00003; Unknown (Box 3)
      Singers; People; Building sites; Instruments; Beezlebubs
    - Beelzebub concert of Alumni at Homecoming, 1977; UA024.001.003.00002.00004; Unknown (Box 3)
      Singers; People; Mayer, Jean; Rafter, Patrick; Marilley, James; Beezlebubs
    - Beelzebub, UA024.001.003.00002.00005; Unknown (Box 3)
      Singers; People; Instruments; Beezlebubs
    - Beelzebub, UA024.001.003.00002.00006; Unknown (Box 3)
      Singers; People; Lampposts; Beezlebubs
    - Beelzebubs, 1966; UA024.001.003.00002.00007; Unknown (Box 3)
      Singers; Beezlebubs
    - Beelzebubs, 1984; UA024.001.003.00002.00008; Unknown (Box 3)
      Singers; People; Interior views; Concerts; Beezlebubs
    - Beelzebubs, UA024.001.003.00002.00009; Unknown (Box 3)
      Singers; People; Building sites; Exterior views; Beezlebubs
    - Beelzebubs, UA024.001.003.00002.00010; Young, Donald T. (Box 3)
    - Beelzebubs, 1965; UA024.001.003.00002.00011; Unknown (Box 3)
      Singers; People; Building sites; Exterior views; Fountains; Beezlebubs
  - Beelzebubs (2), 1966 -- 1986; UA024.001.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - Delta Zeta, 1955; UA024.001.004.00001 (Box 4)
    - Delta Zeta event, 1955; UA024.001.004.00001.00001; Unknown (Box 4)
      Students; Women; Greek letter societies; Parties; Delta Zeta
  - De Molay, 1928; UA024.001.004.00002 (Box 4)
  - Eta Kappa nu, 1963; UA024.001.004.00003 (Box 4)
  - Fraternities, 1955 -- 1959; UA024.001.004.00004 (Box 4)
    - Singing party, 1959; UA024.001.004.00004.00001; Unknown (Box 4)
      Students; People; Men; Women; Singers; Greek letter societies; Piano
    - Fraternity group portrait, 1955; UA024.001.004.00004.00004; Unknown (Box 4)
      People; Men; Greek letter societies
    - Fraternity group portrait, 1955; UA024.001.004.00004.00005; Unknown (Box 4)
  - GE College Bowl, 1962; UA024.001.004.00005 (Box 4)
    - GE College Bowl, 1962; UA024.001.004.00005.00001; Unknown (Box 4)
      People; Students; Men; Women; Student activities; Stone, Steve; Marcovitz, Judith; Boyer, Jay; Tronic, Michael
    - GE College Bowl team with Jumbo, 1962; UA024.001.004.00005.00002; Unknown (Box 4)
      People; Student activities; Students; Men; Women; Stone, Steve; Marcovitz, Judith; Boyer, Jay; Tronic, Michael; Jumbo
  - Glee Club, 1905 -- 1964; UA024.001.004.00006 (Box 4)
    - Glee Club, 1905 -- 1906; UA024.001.004.00006.00002; Unknown (Box 4)
      Men; Student activities; Students; Glee Club
    - Girls Glee Club, 1908; UA024.001.004.00006.00007; Unknown (Box 4)
      Women; Student activities; People; Students; Glee Club
    - Choir, 1964; UA024.001.004.00006.00010; Unknown (Box 4)
      Women; Men; People; Student activities; Students; Singing; Choir
    - Choir rehearsal, 1955; UA024.001.004.00006.00011; Unknown (Box 4)
      Student activities; Students; Singers; Men; Women; Choir
    - Choir, 1955; UA024.001.004.00006.00012; Unknown (Box 4)
      Students; Student activities; Men; Women; Choir
    - Choir, UA024.001.004.00006.00013; Unknown (Box 4)
    - Choir, UA024.001.004.00006.00014; Unknown (Box 4)
      Students; Student activities; Women; Choir
    - Choir, 1964-12; UA024.001.004.00006.00015; Santuria, Neil (Box 4)
    - Choir, UA024.001.004.00006.00016; Unknown (Box 4)
      Students; Student activities; Women; Men; Choir
    - Choir, UA024.001.004.00006.00017; Unknown (Box 4)
      Students; Student activities; Men; Instruments; Choir
    - Christmas Concert, UA024.001.004.00006.00018; Unknown (Box 4)
      Students; Student activities; Men; Singers; Choir
    - Spring Sing, UA024.001.004.00006.00019; Unknown (Box 4)
      Students; Student activities; Men; Singers; Women; People; Choir
    - Candlelight Sing, UA024.001.004.00006.00020; Unknown (Box 4)
      Students; Student activities; Men; Singers; Women; People; Exterior views; Choir
    - Christmas Concert, UA024.001.004.00006.00021; Unknown (Box 4)
      Students; Student activities; Singers; Women; People; Interior views; Choir
    - Concert, UA024.001.004.00006.00022; Unknown (Box 4)
    - Christmas Concert, UA024.001.004.00006.00023; Unknown (Box 4)
  - Hillel, 1944 -- 2014; UA024.001.004.00007 (Box 4)
    - Hillel Home, UA024.001.004.00007.00001; Unknown (Box 4)
      Students; Student activities; People; Interior views; Hillel Foundation
    - From the Center, 2010 -- 2011; UA024.001.004.00007.00002; Tufts Hillel (Box 4)
    - From the Center, 2013 -- 2014; UA024.001.004.00007.00003; Tufts Hillel (Box 4)
  - Historical Society, 1928 -- 1968; UA024.001.004.00008 (Box 4)
  - Inter-Dormitory Council, 1981; UA024.001.004.00009 (Box 4)
  - Interfraternity Council, 1938; UA024.001.004.00010 (Box 4)
    Added play program from accession 2011.015 on 2010-08-20.
    - Inter Fraternity Dance Committee, 1938-11-10; UA024.001.004.00010.00001; Unknown (Box 4)
      Students; Student activities; People; Inter-fraternity Council
  - International Club, 1947 -- 1988; UA024.001.005.00001 (Box 5)
    Includes the following issues of Expressions, A publication of the Tufts Asian Students Club: November 1986; December 1986/January 1987; March 1987; December 1987-January 1988; March-April 1988.
  - International Relations Club, 1935 -- 1962; UA024.001.005.00002 (Box 5)
  - Interscholastic Club, 1909; UA024.001.005.00003 (Box 5)
  - Italian Club, 1921; UA024.001.005.00004 (Box 5)
  - Ivy Society, 1902 -- 1963; UA024.001.005.00005 (Box 5)
    Added Ivy Weekend Program from accession 2011.015 on 2010-08-20.
  - Jackson Day, 1913 -- 1922; UA024.001.005.00006 (Box 5)
  - Jazz Society, UA024.001.005.00007 (Box 5)
  - Jumble, 1951; UA024.001.005.00008 (Box 5)
    Publications moved to UP019.
  - Jumbo Book, 1928 -- 1968; UA024.001.005.00009 (Box 5)
  - Junior Day, 1911 -- 1967; UA024.001.005.00010 (Box 5)
    Added programs from 1963 and 1963 from accession 2011.015 on 2010-08-20.
  - Junior Exhibitions, 1857 -- 1923; UA024.001.005.00011 (Box 5)
  - Key Society, 1958; UA024.001.005.00012 (Box 5)
  - Leonard Carmichael Society, 1964 -- 1980; UA024.001.005.00013 (Box 5)
  - Leonard Carmichael Society, 1950 -- 1980; UA024.001.005.00014 (Box 5)
    - Leonard Carmichael Society, Tutoring session, UA024.001.005.00014.00001 (Box 5)
      Boys; Interior views; Leonard Carmichael Society
    - Leonard Carmichael Society, Kid's Day, UA024.001.005.00014.00002 (Box 5)
      Girls; Leonard Carmichael Society
  - The Luigi Club, UA024.001.005.00015 (Box 5)
  - Mayoralty campaign, 1954 -- 1956; UA024.001.006.00001 (Box 6)
    - Student atop automobile in Mayoralty campaign parade, 1956; UA024.001.006.00001.00001; Unknown (Box 6)
      Mayoralty; Parades; Automobiles; People; Tufts University
    - Tom Denney as Nero on roof, 1956; UA024.001.006.00001.00002; Unknown (Box 6)
      Mayoralty; Students; People; Costumes; Denney, Tom; Tufts University
    - Mayoralty campaign dance, 1956; UA024.001.006.00001.00003; Unknown (Box 6)
      Mayoralty; Crowds; Dances and Dancing; Tufts University
    - Students walking in Mayoralty campaign parade, 1956; UA024.001.006.00001.00004; Hayden, Robert L. (Box 6)
      Mayoralty; Costumes; Parades; Tufts University
    - Students onstage during Mayoralty campaign, 1956; UA024.001.006.00001.00005; Unknown (Box 6)
      Identified on the back: Patricia Hanley.
      Mayoralty; Women; Students; Tufts University
    - Candidate distributing bathtub gin during Mayoralty campaign, 1956; UA024.001.006.00001.00006; Unknown (Box 6)
      Mayoralty; Prohibition; Costumes; Tufts University
    - Music on the campaign wagon, 1956; UA024.001.006.00001.00007; Unknown (Box 6)
      Mayoralty; Music; Students; Tufts University
    - Tom Denney as Nero, 1956; UA024.001.006.00001.00008; Unknown (Box 6)
      Mayoralty; Speeches; Students; Denney, Tom; Tufts University
    - Nero eating grapes and carried by Roman soldiers in Mayoralty campaign parade, 1956; UA024.001.006.00001.00009; Hayden, Robert L. (Box 6)
      Identified on back: Patricia Hanley
      Mayoralty; Parades; Roman; Denney, Tom; Tufts University
    - E. Lawrence Bucky Spurr, Mayoralty campaign, 1954; UA024.001.006.00001.00010; Unknown (Box 6)
      25; "Lets Make Tufts A Year Round Circus!! P.T. 'Bucky' Barnum".
      Mayoralty; Costumes; Portraits; Tufts University
    - Mock marching band, Mayoralty campaign, 1956; UA024.001.006.00001.00011; Unknown (Box 6)
      Mayoralty; Parades; Students; Tufts University
    - 'Nero Presents Tom Denney' souvenir programme, 1956; UA024.001.006.00001.00012; Unknown (Box 6)
      Mayoralty; Programs; Pamphlets; Tufts University
    - Nero, Mayoralty campaign, 1956; UA024.001.006.00001.00013; Unknown (Box 6)
      Image is located inside a pamphlet titled 'Nero Presents Tom Denney'.
      Mayoralty; Costumes; Pamphlets; Denney, Tom; Tufts University
  - The Modern Utopia, 1967; UA024.001.006.00002 (Box 6)
  - Music: Tufts songs sheet music and related correspondence, 1900 -- 1936; UA024.001.006.00003 (Box 6)
    Folder includes one photograph of unidentified singers circa 1910s.
  - Newman Club, 1957 -- 1976; UA024.001.006.00004 (Box 6)
  - Odikon, 1946 -- 1968; UA024.001.006.00005 (Box 6)
  - Omicron Kappa Epsilon (photo), 1950 -- 1960; UA024.001.006.00006 (Box 6)
  - Orchestra, 1929 -- 1935; UA024.001.006.00007 (Box 6)
    - Reese's orchestra on boat, 1929-09-30; UA024.001.006.00007.00001; Unknown (Box 6)
      Music; Instruments; Men; Boats; Students; Tufts University
    - Alpha Tau Omega orchestra, 1930-02-01; UA024.001.006.00007.00002; Unknown (Box 6)
      Music; Instruments; Men; Students; Fraternities; Tufts University
    - Orchestra playing in Goddard, 1935; UA024.001.006.00007.00003; Unknown (Box 6)
      Music; Instruments; Students; Tufts University
    - Musical at Goddard Chapel, 1935-05-07; UA024.001.006.00007.00004; Unknown (Box 6)
    - String quartet in Goddard Chapel, 1932-03-14; UA024.001.006.00007.00005; Unknown (Box 6)
  - Order of the Coffee Pot, 1866 -- 1950; UA024.001.006.00008 (Box 6)
  - Pan Hellenic (general), 1967 -- 1987; UA024.001.006.00009 (Box 6)
  - Pan Hellenic, 1920 -- 1959; UA024.001.006.00010 (Box 6)
  - Pan Hellenic, 1960 -- 1968; UA024.001.006.00011 (Box 6)
  - Pan Hellenic Council, 1954 -- 1961; UA024.001.007.00001 (Box 7)
  - Pan Hellenic: handbooks and manuals, 1967; UA024.001.007.00002 (Box 7)
  - Pan Hellenic Council, 1962 -- 1968; UA024.001.007.00003 (Box 7)
  - Pan Hellenic: hearing, 1957 -- 1960; UA024.001.007.00004 (Box 7)
  - Pan Hellenic: members, 1956 -- 1968; UA024.001.007.00005 (Box 7)
  - Historical Society Record Book, 1924 -- 1937; UA024.001.009.00001 (Box 9)
  - Sword and Shield, 1905 -- 1912; UA024.001.009.00002 (Box 9)
  - Phi Epsilon Pi, 1920 -- 1969; UA024.001.010.00004 (Box 10)
  - Phi Sigma Kappa, 1957 -- 1972; UA024.001.010.00005 (Box 10)
  - Photography Club, 1936 -- 1977; UA024.001.010.00006 (Box 10)
  - Pillar, 1970; UA024.001.010.00007 (Box 10)
  - PIRG, 1973 -- 1975; UA024.001.010.00008 (Box 10)
  - Poetry Club, 1935; UA024.001.010.00009 (Box 10)
  - Political Science Society, newsletter, 1967 -- 1968; UA024.001.011.00001 (Box 11)
  - Pre Medical Society, Constitution, UA024.001.011.00002 (Box 11)
  - Pops Night, 1943 -- 1987; UA024.001.011.00003 (Box 11)
  - Pops Night, 1930 -- 1957; UA024.001.011.00004 (Box 11)
  - Primary Source, 1982 -- 1983; UA024.001.011.00005 (Box 11)
  - Publishing Association, 1891 -- 1912; UA024.001.011.00006 (Box 11)
  - Publishing Association, 1913 -- 1914; UA024.001.012.00001 (Box 12)
  - Publishing Association, 1904 -- 1910; UA024.001.012.00002 (Box 12)
  - Publishing Association, Secretary's book, 1900; UA024.001.012.00003 (Box 12)
  - Publishing Association, Constitution and by-laws, 1891; UA024.001.012.00004 (Box 12)
  - Publishing Association, 1900 -- 1910; UA024.001.012.00005 (Box 12)
  - Reading Room Association, 1893 -- 1916; UA024.001.013.00001 (Box 13)
  - Radio Society, 1915 -- 1961; UA024.001.013.00002 (Box 13)
  - Radio Stations, 1948 -- 1968; UA024.001.013.00003 (Box 13)
  - Religious Council, 1954; UA024.001.013.00004 (Box 13)
  - Religious organizations, 1902 -- 1947; UA024.001.013.00005 (Box 13)
  - Rodin Society, 1951; UA024.001.013.00006 (Box 13)
  - Students for a Democratic Society, 1967 -- 1971; UA024.001.013.00007 (Box 13)
  - S.P.I.R.I.T., 1982; UA024.001.013.00008 (Box 13)
  - Sigma Kappa, 1935 -- 1956; UA024.001.013.00009 (Box 13)
  - Sigma Omega Psi, 1922; UA024.001.013.00010 (Box 13)
  - Sigma Pi Sigma, 1947; UA024.001.013.00011 (Box 13)
  - Sigma Tau Alpha, 1916 -- 1937; UA024.001.013.00012 (Box 13)
  - Society of Scholars, 1969; UA024.001.013.00013 (Box 13)
  - Spree Club, 1887; UA024.001.013.00014 (Box 13)
  - Sororities, 1923 -- 1950; UA024.001.013.00015 (Box 13)
  - Strike News, 1970; UA024.001.013.00016 (Box 13)
  - Students Concerned about racism (SCAR), 1968 -- 1970; UA024.001.013.00017 (Box 13)
  - Student Council, general, 1909 -- 1966; UA024.001.013.00018 (Box 13)
  - Student Council, correspondence and minutes, 1912 -- 1966; UA024.001.013.00019 (Box 13)
  - Students for Tufts, 1969; UA024.001.016.00001 (Box 16)
  - Student publications, 1929 -- 1964; UA024.001.016.00002 (Box 16)
  - Stuft Club, 1887; UA024.001.016.00003 (Box 16)
  - Sword and Shield, 1915 -- 1956; UA024.001.016.00004 (Box 16)
  - Tau Beta Pi, 1938 -- 1972; UA024.001.016.00005 (Box 16)
  - TUTV (Tufts University Television), 1977 -- 1981; UA024.001.016.00006 (Box 16)
  - Tau Epsilon Phi, 1961; UA024.001.016.00007 (Box 16)
  - Thalia Sorority, 1958 -- 1960; UA024.001.016.00008 (Box 16)
  - Theta Delta Chi, 1920 -- 1970; UA024.001.016.00009 (Box 16)
  - Theta Delta Chi, 1958; UA024.001.016.00010 (Box 16)
  - Theta Chi, 1978 -- 1979; UA024.001.016.00011 (Box 16)
  - Theta Delta Theta, 1903 -- 1963; UA024.001.016.00012 (Box 16)
  - Today Tufts, 1970 -- 1979; UA024.001.016.00013 (Box 16)
  - Tower Cross, 1965 -- 1975; UA024.001.016.00014 (Box 16)
    Added event programs from accession 2011.015 on 2010-08-20.
  - Torn Ticket, 1923 -- 1984; UA024.001.016.00015 (Box 16)
  - Tuftonian, 1967 -- 1975; UA024.001.016.00016 (Box 16)
  - Tuf-Tonic, 1950 -- 1976; UA024.001.016.00017 (Box 16)
    Includes Vol. 1, no. 1-Vol. 1, no. 4 of the Tuf-Tonic publication.
  - Tufts Arts Association, 1978; UA024.001.016.00018 (Box 16)
  - Tufts Astronomical Society, 1946 -- 1969; UA024.001.016.00019 (Box 16)
  - Tufts Coalition on Human Rights, 1923; UA024.001.016.00020 (Box 16)
  - Tufts Chorus, 1946 -- 1969; UA024.001.016.00021
  - Tufts College Press Club, 1923; UA024.001.016.00022
  - Tufts Community Union, general, 1969 -- 1970; UA024.001.017.00001 (Box 17)
  - TCU, Constitution, organizations, 1968 -- 1985; UA024.001.017.00002 (Box 17)
  - TCU Evaluations, 1973 -- 1984; UA024.001.017.00003 (Box 17)
  - Course Evaluation Guide, Spring, 1995; UA024.001.017.00004 (Box 17)
  - Course Evaluation Guide, Spring, 1991; UA024.001.017.00005 (Box 17)
  - Course Evaluation Guide, 1987 -- 1988; UA024.001.017.00006 (Box 17)
  - Course Evaluation Guide, 1986 -- 1987; UA024.001.017.00007 (Box 17)
  - The Tufts Review, 1984 -- 1985; UA024.001.017.00008 (Box 17)
  - Course Evaluation Booklet, Fall, 1983; UA024.001.017.00009 (Box 17)
  - The Inside Track, 1983; UA024.001.017.00010 (Box 17)
  - Course Evaluations, Spring, 1980; UA024.001.017.00011 (Box 17)
  - Course Evaluations, Fall, 1981; UA024.001.017.00012 (Box 17)
  - Course Evaluations, Fall, 1978; UA024.001.018.00001 (Box 18)
  - Course Evaluations, Spring, 1978; UA024.001.018.00002 (Box 18)
  - Course Evaluations, Fall, 1977; UA024.001.018.00003 (Box 18)
  - Course Evaluations, Spring, 1977; UA024.001.018.00004 (Box 18)
  - Course Evaluations, Spring, 1976; UA024.001.018.00005 (Box 18)
  - Course Evaluations, Fall, 1975; UA024.001.018.00006 (Box 18)
  - Course Evaluations, Spring, 1975; UA024.001.018.00007 (Box 18)
  - Course Evaluations, Spring, 1975; UA024.001.018.00008 (Box 18)
  - Course Evaluations, Fall, 1973; UA024.001.018.00009 (Box 18)
  - Course Evaluations, Fall, 1974; UA024.001.018.00010 (Box 18)
  - Tufts Council on International Affairs, 1975; UA024.001.019.00001 (Box 19)
  - Tufts gay community, 1978; UA024.001.019.00002 (Box 19)
  - Tufts Lesbian, Gay & Bisexual Center, 1992; UA024.001.019.00003 (Box 19)
  - Tufts lesbian, gay & bisexual community, 1 of 2, 1980 -- 1994; UA024.001.019.00004a (Box 19)
  - Tufts lesbian, gay & bisexual community, 2 of 2, 1980 -- 1994; UA024.001.019.00004b (Box 19)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, 1968; UA024.001.019.00005 (Box 19)
  - Tufts Hunger Action Project, 1977; UA024.001.019.00006 (Box 19)
  - Tufts-Jackson Civil Rights Committee, 1962; UA024.001.019.00007 (Box 19)
  - Tufts Liberal Union, 1948; UA024.001.019.00008 (Box 19)
  - Tufts Mountain Club, 1944 -- 1973; UA024.001.019.00009 (Box 19)
  - Tufts Navy Club, 1948; UA024.001.019.00010 (Box 19)
  - Tufts Opera Theater, UA024.001.019.00011 (Box 19)
  - Tufts Peace Committee, 1936; UA024.001.019.00012 (Box 19)
  - Tufts Political Action Coalition, 1971 -- 1979; UA024.001.019.00013 (Box 19)
  - Tufts Political Action Coalition, participant, 1981 -- 1986; UA024.001.019.00014 (Box 19)
  - Tufts Sanctuary Committee, 1986; UA024.001.019.00015 (Box 19)
  - Tufts Student Resources, 1962 -- 1981; UA024.001.019.00016 (Box 19)
  - Tufts Student Union, 1940; UA024.001.019.00017 (Box 19)
  - Tufts Students for the Exploration and Development of Space stickers, circa 2019; UA024.000424; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 8)
    Gift of Jeffrey Blitt of Tufts SEDS, 2019, accession MS-2019-078.
  - Tufts Timepiece, 1922; UA024.001.019.00018 (Box 19)
  - Tufts Union, 1924; UA024.001.019.00019 (Box 19)
  - Tufts Unity Club (The Beacon), 1959 -- 1960; UA024.001.020.00001 (Box 20)
  - Tufts War Activities Board, 1943; UA024.001.020.00002 (Box 20)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1934 -- 1966; UA024.001.020.00003 (Box 20)
  - Tufts Weekly account book, 1900 -- 1908; UA024.001.020.00004 (Box 20)
  - Tufts Women Center, 1975 -- 1980; UA024.001.020.00005 (Box 20)
  - Tufts Yacht Club, 1944 -- 1958; UA024.001.022.00007 (Box 22)
  - United World Federalist, 1946 -- 1947; UA024.001.022.00001 (Box 22)
  - Veterans Club (WWII), 1945; UA024.001.022.00002 (Box 22)
  - Vital Issues, 1960 -- 1961; UA024.001.022.00003 (Box 22)
  - Young Americans for Freedom, 1962; UA024.001.022.00004 (Box 22)
  - WMFO, 1971 -- 1985; UA024.001.022.00005 (Box 22)
  - Zeta Psi, 1893 -- 1950; UA024.001.022.00006; 0.1 Linear Feet (Box 22)
    This file contains photographs and correspondence from members of Zeta Psi, as well as a brass-covered dance card for a Zeta Psi Fraternity Dance held at the Goddard Gymnasium on March 14, 1913.
    Dance card was donated by Teresa Nowak, 2022, accession MS-2023-021.
- Photographs, 1894 -- 1982; 1912 -- 1982; UA024.002; 1.7 Linear Feet; 18 Digital Object(s)
  Loose prints from the Activities and Organizations collection.
  This series is arranged as found.
  - Tom Meyers (seated), with (from left to right) Glen Peterson, Bill Hallarn, Phil Thompson and Nils Yngve Wessell, 1953; UA024.002.023.00001; Unknown (Box 23)
    People; Students; College administrators; Meyers, Tom; Peterson, Glen; Hallarn, Bill; Thompson, Phil; Wessell, Nils Yngve; Tufts University
  - Dormitory move-in, 1960; UA024.002.023.00002; Unknown (Box 23)
    People; Students; Dormitories; Tufts University
  - Students seated around Jumbo statue, 1950; UA024.002.023.00003; Unknown (Box 23)
    People; Students; Statues; Tufts University
  - Sackler School class of 1982 on Memorial Steps, UA024.002.023.00004; Unknown (Box 23)
    People; Graduate students; Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences
  - Photography instruction, 1967; UA024.002.023.00005; Unknown (Box 23)
    People; Students; Photographs; Tufts University
  - Tufts students at unidentified outdoor function, 1964; UA024.002.023.00006; Unknown (Box 23)
    People; Student activities; Students; Tufts University
  - Costumed students performing at unidentified function, 1960; UA024.002.023.00007; Unknown (Box 23)
    Student activities; Students; Performance artists; Costumes; Cycling; Singers; Dances and Dancing; Tufts University
  - Junior dinner dance, 1960; UA024.002.023.00008; Unknown (Box 23)
    People; Dances and Dancing; Balls; Dinners and Dining; Students; Tufts University
  - Transfer students, March, 1970; UA024.002.023.00009 (Box 23)
    Students; Tufts University
  - Pan Hellenic Christmas Sing, 1948; UA024.002.023.00010; Coyne, J. Stirling (Box 23)
    Students; Women; Singers; Christmas Sing; Pan Hellenic Society
  - Tufts band, April, 1966; UA024.002.023.00011; Unknown (Box 23)
    People; Music and musical performances; Student activities; Students; Tufts University
  - Tufts band, 1964; UA024.002.023.00012; Sentura, Neil (Box 23)
    People; Music and musical performances; Students; Student activities; Tufts University
  - Food service worker serves Tufts students at unidentified function, 1960; UA024.002.023.00013; Duette (Box 23)
    Students; Food service; Workers; Tufts University
  - Tufts College Musical Clubs, 1913 -- 1914; UA024.002.023.00014 (Box Small Map Case 2 Drawer 4)
    This photograph was found uncatalogued in the stacks in summer 2007. Note its different location; it is housed in a separate box with other oversize materials.
  - Tufts College Musical Clubs, 1916 -- 1917; UA024.002.023.00015 (Box Small Map Case 2 Drawer 4)
  - Tufts College Musical Clubs, 1903 -- 1904; UA024.002.023.00016 (Box Small Map Case 2 Drawer 4)
  - Tufts College Musical Clubs, 1908 -- 1909; UA024.002.023.00017 (Box Small Map Case 2 Drawer 4)
  - Theta Delta Chi photograph, 1913; UA024.002.023.00018 (Box Shared 35)
    - Theta Delta Chi, 1913; UA024.002.023.00018.00001; Unknown (Box Shared 35)
      Men; People; Fraternities; Theta Delta Chi
  - Fraternity photograph, 1914; UA024.002.023.00019 (Box Shared 35)
    Probably Theta Delta Chi. This photograph was found uncatalogued in the stacks in summer 2007. Note its different location; it is housed in a separate box with other oversize materials.
    - Unidentified fraternity, 1914; UA024.002.023.00019.00001; Unknown (Box Shared 35)
      Possibly Theta Delta Chi fraternity.
  - Theta Delta Chi photograph, 1915; UA024.002.023.00020 (Box Shared 35)
    - Theta Delta Chi, 1915; UA024.002.023.00020.00001; Unknown (Box Shared 35)
      People; Men; Fraternities; Theta Delta Chi
  - Tufts College Musical Clubs, 1894 -- 1895; UA024.002.023.00021 (Box Shared 4)
  - Tufts Glee, Mandolin, and Guitar Clubs, 1894 -- 1895; UA024.002.023.00022 (Box Shared 4)
  - Tufts Glee Club, 1906; UA024.002.023.00023 (Box Shared 4)
  - Tufts Glee and Mandolin Club, 1904 -- 1905; UA024.002.023.00024 (Box Shared 4)
  - Tufts Glee, Mandolin, and Guitar Clubs, 1915 -- 1916; UA024.002.023.00025 (Box Shared 4)
  - Tufts Musical Clubs, 1914 -- 1915; UA024.002.023.00026 (Box Shared 4)